into It Won't Stop Coming Out Friday.
(Leonard:)Hey, how about
that Asian fusion place?
(Sheldon:)Fusion and Asians?
(Sheldon:)I'm trying not to
think about science.
(Penny:)What the hell?
What... she's not working late!
(Sheldon:)-And Amy doesn't look sick.
-Why would they lie to us?
(Sheldon:)That's a good question.
(Sheldon:)Amy and Bernadette.
(Sheldon:)Why did you lie to us?
(Raj:)Hey. Listen to this.
"Murder, cannibalism
and satanic rituals
are just a few of the thousand-plus
horrors that await."
(Howard:)I just helped my mom
out of the tub,
(Howard:)so I'm one slippery horror
ahead of you.
(Raj:)You're a good son.
I don't know how you do it.
(Howard:)Beach blankets, my friend.
It's all about beach blankets.
(Sheldon:)All right,
let's get this over with.